Harold Stein Filk Collection
Harold Stein Filk Archive
- Conventions
  - GAFilk
    - GAFilk 17, 2015
      - GAFilk 17 Program booklet, 2015; GAFilk; GAFilk 17 (2015); 1 copy; Notes: This is a yellow covered stapled booklet from 2015. The guests were GOH: S.J. Tucker, Toasmasters: The Blibbering Humdingers, Interfilk Guest: C.D. Woodbury, Super Secret Guest: Robin W. Baily, and featuring Play It With Moxie! ConCom's Choice concert: Marc Gunn Origin: GAFilk 2015 Convention: GAFilk 17: 2015; genreform: Program booklet (Box 2)
        Convention -- GAFilk 17 (2015); Program booklet
      - GAFilk 2015, Program Book, GAFilk 17 (2015); 1 copy; Notes: Yellow booklet Origin: GAFilk 2015, January 9-11 Convention: GAFilk 17: 2015; genreform: Program Book (Box 8)
        Convention -- GAFilk 17 (2015); Program Book
      - GAFilk 17, Program book, 2015; GAFilk 19 (2017); GAFilk 17 (2015); 1 copy; Origin: GAFilk 2015, January 9-11; genreform: Program booklet (Box 7)
    - GAFilk 18, 08 Jan 2016 to 10 Jan 2016
      - GAFilk 18 Songbook, 2016; GAFilk 18 (2016); 1 copy; Notes: Red cover, spiral bound - Limited edition printing 30/45 Origin: GAFilk 2016, January 8-10, 2016 Convention: GAFilk 18: 2016; genreform: Songbook (Box 9)
        Convention -- GAFilk 18 (2016); Songbook
      - GAFilk Program booklet, 8 January 2016; GAFilk 18 (2016); GAFilk; 1 copy; Notes: Orange booklet Origin: GAFilk Convention: GAFilk 18: 2016; genreform: Program booklet (Box 7)
        Convention -- GAFilk 18 (2016); Program booklet
    - GaFilk 19, 06 Jan 2017 to 08 Jan 2017
      - GAFilk 2017 Program booklet, 6 January 2017; GAFilk 19 (2017); 3 copy; Notes: Yellow booklet Convention: GAFilk 19: 2017; genreform: Program booklet (Box 7)
        Convention -- GAFilk 19 (2017); Program booklet
      - GAFilk 2017 Pocket Program, GAFilk 19 (2017); 1 copy; Notes: Yellow cover, pocket program Origin: GaFilk 2018, January 6-8, 2017; genreform: Pocket Program (Box 9)
        Might really be GaFilk 20: 2018
        Convention -- GAFilk 19 (2017); Program book -- Pocket program
        - Leslie Hudson Set List, 2017; GAFilk 19 (2017); 1 copy; Notes: Four handwritten pages. Set list: Double Trouble, Sister & Sinners, Call the Doctor, Leslie might be Leslie Hudson, For a While, Oars in the Water, Troublemaker, Black Belt, Feel It All, Vasilisa Trilogy, Any Wya the Wind Blows Origin: GAFilk 2017 Convention: GAFilk 19: 2017; genreform: Set list (Box 7)
          Convention -- GAFilk 19 (2017); Set list
    - GaFilk 20, 05 Jan 2018 to 07 Jan 2018
      - GAFilk 20 Songbook, 2018; GAFilk 20 (2018); 1 copy; Notes: Three piece green and white cover with Emerald, limited edition songbook 1/36 Origin: January 5-7, 2018 Convention: GaFilk 20: 2018; genreform: Songbook (Box 9)
        Convention -- GaFilk 20 (2018); Songbook
      - GAFilk 2018 Pocket Program, GAFilk 20 (2018); 1 copy; Notes: Goldenrod cover, pocket program Origin: GaFilk 2018, January 5-7, 2018 Convention: GaFilk 20: 2018; genreform: Pocket Program (Box 9)
        Convention -- GaFilk 20 (2018); Program book -- Pocket program
  - Heliosphere
    - Heliosphere 2018
  - I-CON
    - I-Con 8, 1989
    - I-Con 2008
    - I-CON 2011
    - Frank Hayes at I-Con 2002 (Concert ?) Has some skips, tracks labelled at least some 41 tracks 98:26, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 008 eighth box of minidiscs #11 Origin: Convention: I-CON 21: 2002; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
      Convention -- I-CON 21: 2002; MiniDisc
    - I-Con 21-1 Fri. Sat. 4/19-20/02, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 008 eighth box of minidiscs #8 Origin: Convention: I-CON 21: 2002; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - I-Con 21-2 Sat 4/20/02 Panels, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 008 eighth box of minidiscs #12 Origin: Convention: I-CON 21: 2002; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - I-Con 21-4 Sat 4/20/02 Concert and Caberet, 1 copy; Notes: Mini - 008 eighth box of minidiscs #13 Origin: Convention: I-CON 21: 2002; genreform: MiniDisc (Box 17)
    - I-Con Friday Night OPEN Filk (Sat not recorded) Disco 2 of 2 4/08, 2008; I-Con 2008; Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: I-Con 2008; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
      Convention -- I-Con 2008; CD -- Burnt
    - I-Con 2008 RAW recordings - Disc 1 of 2 Concerts 4/08, I-Con 2008; Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: I-Con 2008; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
    - Souvenir Program Guide, 1 copy; Notes: People with riding biped, on alien world. Staple bound Origin: Convention: I-CON 27: 2008; genreform: Program Book (Box 14)
      Convention -- I-CON 27: 2008; Program Book
    - Souvenir Program Guide, 1 copy; Notes: Abstract red dragon on elaborate background, staple bound Origin: Convention: I-CON 28: 2009; genreform: Program Book (Box 14)
      Convention -- I-CON 28: 2009; Program Book
    - I-Con 8 Pocket Program, 1989; I-Con 8 1989; 1 copy; Notes: Four sheet fold out with map and schedule Origin: I-Con 8 1989 Convention: I-Con 8 1989; genreform: Pocket Program (Box 9)
      Convention -- I-Con 8 1989; Program book -- Pocket program
  - InConJunction
    - InConJunction XIV, 01 Jul 1994 to 03 Jul 1994
      Indianapolis, IN
  - LICon
    - LICon 2014
  - Lunacon
    - Lunacon 49, 17 Mar 2006 to 20 Mar 2006
      Meadowlands, NJ
    - Lunacon 50, 16 Mar 2007 to 18 Mar 2007
      Rye Brook, NY.
    - Lunacon 51, 14 Mar 2008 to 16 Mar 2008
    - Lunacon 2014, 14 Mar 2014 to 16 Mar 2016
    - Lunacon 2016, 18 Mar 2016 to 20 Mar 2016
    - Lunacon 2017, 07 Apr 2017 to 09 Apr 2017
      Tarrytown, NY
    - Harold's schedule from a Lunacon, Lunacon (?); 1 copy; Origin: Probably from a Lunacon Convention: Lunacon (?); genreform: Schedule (Box 7)
      Convention -- Lunacon; Schedule
    - Rogow Lunacon 2006 concert, Chapin Concerts, 9/06 Housefilk, Lunacon 2006; Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: Lunacon 49; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
      Convention -- Lunacon 49 (2006); CD -- Burnt
    - Friday, SAT afternoon concerts, Fantasy Theme Circle, Lunacon 2007, Disc 1 of 3, Lunacon 2007; Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Not all of Harold's Disc X of Y labels are accurate. Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: Lunacon 50; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
      Convention -- Lunacon 50 (2007); CD -- Burnt
    - Lunacon 2007 Disc 3 of 3, Lunacon 2007; Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Not all of Harold's Disc X of Y labels are accurate. Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: Lunacon 50; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
    - Sat open filk, Funny Things concert, Science Theme circle, Lunacon 2007, Disc 2 of 3, Lunacon 2007; Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: The Funny Things are Merav Hoffman and Batya Wittenberg (and friends) Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: Lunacon 50; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
    - Lunacon 2014 Pocket Program, Lunacon 2014, March 14-16, 2014; 1 copy; Notes: Pocket program, blue cover Convention: Lunacon 57, March 14-16, 2014; genreform: Pocket Program (Box 9)
      Convention -- Lunacon 2014; Program book -- Pocket program
    - Lunacon 2014 Program Book, Lunacon 2014, March 14-16, 2014; 1 copy; Notes: Glossy Program book Convention: Lunacon 57, March 14-16, 2014; genreform: Program Book (Box 9)
      Convention -- Lunacon 2014; Program Book
    - Lunacon 2016 program book, March 18-20, 2016, Lunacon 2016; 1 copy; Notes: This is a full sized program book with a colored cover depicting a space station. The guests were: GOHs were Robert J. Sawyer, Rick Sternbach and Naomi Novik, Music Guests were Murder Ballads Origin: Lunacon 2016 Convention: Lunacon 58; genreform: Color program book (Box 2)
      Convention -- Lunacon 2016; Color program book
    - Lunacon 2016, pocket program, Lunacon 2016; 1 copy; Notes: This is a blue covered pocket program with the Lunacon mascot on the cover, reading a book. Origin: Lunacon 2016 Convention: Lunacon 58; genreform: Pocket program (Box 2)
      Convention -- Lunacon 2016; Program book -- Pocket program
    - Lunacon 2017 Program Book, Lunacon 2017; 1 copy; Notes: Space scene cover Convention: Lunacon 59; genreform: Program Book (Box 8)
      Convention -- Lunacon 2017; Program Book
    - Lunacon 51, March 14-16, 2008, Lunacon 51; 1 copy; Notes: This is a pink covered pocket program with the Lunacon mascot, sitting in a sliver of the moon reading a book. Origin: Lunacon 2008 Convention: Lunacon 51; genreform: Pocket program (Box 2)
      Convention -- Lunacon 51 (2008); Program book -- Pocket program
    - Lunacon 2017 Program Grid, Lunacon 2017; 1 copy; Notes: Yellow, double sided Origin: Lunacon 2017 Convention: Lunacon 60: 2017; genreform: Program Grid (Box 8)
      Convention -- Lunacon 2017; Program Grid
    - Lunacon 2013, Fish, Leslie; 1 copy; Notes: This was the year Leslie Fish was musical guest Origin: Convention: Lunacon 2013; genreform: Program Book (Box 9)
      Convention -- Lunacon 2013; Program Book
  - Marcon
    - Marcon 29, 13 May 1994 to 15 May 1994
      Columbus, OH
    - Marcon 37, 24 May 2002 to 26 May 2002
  - MarsCon
    - MarsCon 2008
    - The MarsCon 2008 Dementia Track Fund Raiser CD! Disc 2, MarsCon 2008; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Compiled by Luke Sienkowski (aka The Great Luke Ski) Convention: MarsCon 2008; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      Convention -- MarsCon 2008; CD -- Commercial
    - The MarsCon 2008 Dementia Track Fund Raiser CD! Disc 1, MarsCon 2008; Compiled by Luke Sienkowski (aka The Great Luke Ski); 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Compiled by Luke Sienkowski (aka The Great Luke Ski) Convention: MarsCon 2008; genreform: Premium CD (Box 3)
      Convention -- MarsCon 2008; CD -- Premium
  - Minicon
  - NASFic, NASFic occurs in years when WorldCon is held outside North America to 08 Aug 2010
    - NASFic 10: Reconstruction, 05 Aug 2010
      Raleigh, NC
      - Reconstruction Pocket Program, 2010; 1 copy; Notes: Robot with lost hand cover. Pamphlet style. Staple bound Origin: Convention: NASFic 10: Reconstruction: 2010; genreform: Pocket program (Box 14)
        Convention -- NASFic 10. Reconstruction (2010); Program book -- Pocket program
      - Reconstruction Pocket Program, 2010; 1 copy; Notes: Robot with lost hand cover. Pamphlet style. Staple bound Origin: Convention: NASFic 10: Reconstruction: 2010; genreform: Pocket program (Box 14)
    - NASFIC 11: Detcon 1, 17 Jul 2014 to 20 Jul 2014
      Detroit, Michigan
      - DetCon 2014 Setlist for the band Cheshire Moon, Cheshire Moon; 1 copy; Notes: Acoustic set: Out of the Light, Disenchanted, Cuatro: Critters, DADGAG: Widow's Garden, Snow White, Red Road, Masters of Library Science Origin: Eric and Lizzie Convention: NASFIC 11: Detcon 1; genreform: Set list (Box 7)
        Convention -- NASFIC 11. Detcon 1 (2014); Set list
      - InterConBustion the 11th Occasional NASFIC - Newsletter of Detcon 1, 17 July 2014; Detcon 1; 2 copy; Notes: Daily convention newsletter, morning edition Origin: 41837 Convention: NASFIC 11: Detcon 1; genreform: Newsletter (Box 9)
        Convention -- NASFIC 11. Detcon 1 (2014); Newsletter
      - Programming updates, 17 July 2014; Detcon 1; 1 copy; Origin: 41837 Convention: NASFIC 11: Detcon 1; genreform: Programming updates (Box 9)
        Convention -- NASFIC 11. Detcon 1 (2014); Programming updates
      - InterConBustion the 11th Occasional NASFIC - Newsletter of Detcon 1, 18 July 2014; Detcon 1; 1 copy; Notes: Daily convention newsletter, morning edition Origin: 41838 Convention: NASFIC 11: Detcon 1; genreform: Newsletter (Box 9)
      - InterConBustion the 11th Occasional NASFIC - Newsletter of Detcon 1, 19 July 2014; Detcon 1; 1 copy; Notes: Daily convention newsletter, evening edition Origin: 41839 Convention: NASFIC 11: Detcon 1; genreform: Newsletter (Box 9)
      - InterConBustion the 11th Occasional NASFIC - Newsletter of Detcon 1, 20 July 2014; Detcon 1; 1 copy; Notes: Daily convention newsletter Origin: 41840 Convention: NASFIC 11: Detcon 1; genreform: Newsletter (Box 9)
      - Detcon 1, 2014; 1 copy; Notes: Updates to programing from Friday of the con Origin: Convention: NASFIC 11: Detcon 1; genreform: Programming updates (Box 9)
      - Detcon 1 Program Book, 2014; Detcon 1; 1 copy; Notes: Glossy program book Origin: Convention: NASFIC 11: Detcon 1; genreform: Program Book (Box 9)
        Convention -- NASFIC 11. Detcon 1 (2014); Program Book
      - Detcon 1 Restaurant Guide, 2014; Detcon 1; 1 copy; Origin: Convention: NASFIC 11: Detcon 1; genreform: Restaurant Guide (Box 9)
        Convention -- NASFIC 11. Detcon 1 (2014); Restaurant Guide
      - Detcon 1, 2014; Detcon 1, July 17 - July 20; 1 copy; Notes: White pocket format Origin: Detcon 1, July 17 - July 20 Convention: NASFIC 11: Detcon 1; genreform: Pocket Program (Box 8)
        Convention -- NASFIC 11. Detcon 1 (2014); Program book -- Pocket program
      - Hoax newsletter of Detcon 1 - Titled BOOM!, 24 July 2014; 1 copy; Notes: Hoax newsletter making fun of actual newsletter Origin: 41844 Convention: NASFIC 11: Detcon 1; genreform: Newsletter (Box 9)
      - Detcon 1 Set List for Stone Dragons, 2014; Stone Dragons; 1 copy; Notes: Band lineup includes Tom Jeffers, Sue Jeffers, Karen, Phil, Jane as well as Howard and Peggi Origin: Convention: NASFIC 11: Detcon 1; genreform: Set list (Box 9)
  - NEFilk
    - NEFilk 1: ConCerto 1990, 08 Jun 1990 to 10 Jun 1990
      Cherry Hill, NJ; Convention -- NEFilk 1. ConCerto 1990; Convention -- NEFilk
      - ConCerto 1990 Program Book, NEFilk 1. ConCerto 1990; 1 copy; Notes: Duplicate Origin: ConCerto 1990 Convention: ConCerto 1990; genreform: Program Book (Box 10)
        Convention -- NEFilk 1. ConCerto 1990; Program Book
    - NEFilk 2: Concertino 1992, 19 Jun 1992 to 21 Jun 1992
      Woburn, MA
      - Program book, 1992; 1 copy; Notes: Blue cover, spiral bound Origin: NEFilk Convention: NEFilk 2: Concertino 1992; genreform: Songbook|Program Book (Box 13)
        Convention -- NEFilk 2. Concertino 1992; Songbook; Program Book
    - NEFIlk 3: Conterpoint 1, 04 Jun 1993 to 06 Jun 1993
      Baltimore, MD; Convention -- NEFilk 3. Conterpoint 1 (1993); Convention -- NEFilk
      - Fri concert 1 - Conterpoint, 1991; 1 copy; Convention: NEFIlk 3: Conterpoint 1: 1993; genreform: Tape (Box 17)
        Convention -- NEFilk 3. Conterpoint 1 (1993); Tape
      - Fri concert 2, open filk 1 - Conterpoint, 1993; 1 copy; Convention: NEFIlk 3: Conterpoint 1: 1993; genreform: Tape (Box 17)
      - Fri Open Filk 2 Conterpoint, 1993; 1 copy; Convention: NEFIlk 3: Conterpoint 1: 1993; genreform: Tape (Box 17)
      - Sat Concert 3 Conterpoint, 1993; 1 copy; Notes: Probably Conterpoint 1 Convention: NEFIlk 3: Conterpoint 1: 1993; genreform: Tape (Box 17)
      - Sat Open 4, Sun Concert 1 - Conterpoint, 1993; 1 copy; Convention: NEFIlk 3: Conterpoint 1: 1993; genreform: Tape (Box 17)
      - Sun Concert 2 Conterpoint, 1993; 1 copy; Notes: Probably Conterpoint 1 Convention: NEFIlk 3: Conterpoint 1: 1993; genreform: Tape (Box 17)
    - NEFilk 4: Contata 1994, 10 Jun 1994 to 13 Jun 1994
      Secaucus, NJ; Convention -- NEFilk 4. Contata 1994; Convention -- NEFilk
      - Very scratched copy of Take Out, 1994; NEFilk 4. Contata 1994; Siren Song Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Siren Song Studios Convention: NEFilk 4: Contata 1994; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 1)
        Convention -- NEFilk 4. Contata 1994; CD -- Burnt
      - Take Out, 1994; NEFilk 4. Contata 1994; Siren Song Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Siren Song Studios Convention: NEFilk 4: Contata 1994; genreform: Limited Edition CD (Box 1)
        Convention -- NEFilk 4. Contata 1994; CD -- Limited Edition
    - NEFilk 10
      - Program Book, June 16-18, 2000; 1 copy; Notes: Beige cover with Clam Chowder, Joe Bethancourt and and Lynn Gold on cover Origin: Convention: Conterpoint 3; genreform: Songbook|Program Book (Box 13)
        Convention -- NEFilk 10. Conterpoint 3 (2000); Songbook; Program Book
    - NEFilk 11: Conterpoint IV, 22 Jun 2001 to 24 Jun 2001
      Rockville, MD; Convention -- NEFilk 11. Conterpoint IV (2001); Convention -- NEFilk
      - Conterpoint Four, 2001; NEFilk 11. Conterpoint Four (June 22-24, 2001); 1 copy; Notes: Stapled together, whitish cover Origin: Conterpoint Four, June 22-24, 2001 Convention: NEFilk 11: Conterpoint IV; genreform: Program Book (Box 10)
        Convention -- NEFilk 11. Conterpoint IV (2001); Program Book
    - NEFilk 13: ConCertino '03, 18 Jul 2003 to 20 Jul 2003
      Worcester, MA; Convention -- NEFilk 13. ConCertino '03 (2003); Convention -- NEFilk
      - Copyright Challenged, 2003; NEFilk 13. ConCertino '03 (2003); 1 copy; Origin: Concertino 2003 Convention: NEFilk 13: ConCertino '03; genreform: Premium CD (Box 3)
        Convention -- NEFilk 13. ConCertino '03 (2003); CD -- Premium
      - The Scared Harp: Choral arrangements of filk songs, 2003; 1 copy; Notes: First printing, #57/100 Origin: www.mewsic.com/TheScaredHarp Convention: NEFilk 13: ConCertino '03; genreform: Songbook (Box 13)
        Convention -- NEFilk 13. ConCertino '03 (2003); Songbook
      - Program book Conterpoint 2004, 1 copy; Notes: Cicadas storm the whitehouse cover on green paper, spiral bound, Gary McGath, editor Origin: NEFilk 14 Convention: NEFilk 14: Conterpoint 2004; genreform: Songbook|Program Book (Box 13)
        Convention -- NEFilk 14. Conterpoint 2004; Songbook; Program Book
    - NEFilk 15: Contata 2005, 24 Jun 2005 to 26 Jun 2005
      Secaucus, NJ; Convention -- NEFilk 15. Contata 2005; Convention -- NEFilk
      - Contata 2005 Songbook, NEFilk 15. Contata 2005 (June 24-25, 2005); 2 copy; Notes: Spiral bound, green cover with Musical instruments playing poker by Avram Grumer Origin: Contata 2005/NYMFO Convention: NEFilk 15: Contata 2005; genreform: Songbook (Box 10, Box 16)
        Convention -- NEFilk 15. Contata 2005; Songbook
    - NEFilk 16
      - Worcester Restaurant Guide v.3.0, an opinionated guide to mid-scale eating, 2006; Concertino 2006 Restaurant Guide, Revised 2006; 1 copy; Notes: Three pages, double sided, with maps and grids, and snark Origin: Concertino 2006 Restaurant Guide, Revised 2006 Convention: NEFilk 16: Concertino 2006; genreform: Restaurant Guide (Box 10)
        Convention -- NEFilk 16. Concertino 2006; Restaurant Guide
      - Concertino 2006 Songbook, Concertinto 2006, June 16-18, 2006; 1 copy; Notes: Black cover with eyes, and jokes, spoiral bound Origin: Concertinto 2006 Convention: Concertinto 2006, June 16-18, 2006; genreform: Songbook (Box 10)
        Convention -- NEFilk 16. Concertino 2006; Songbook
    - NEFilk 17: Conterpoint 2007, 22 Jun 2007 to 24 Jun 2007
      Rockville, MD; Convention -- NEFilk 17. Conterpoint 2007; Convention -- NEFilk
      - ConterPoint 2007 Large Files PC Readable, NEFilk 17. Conterpoint 2007; Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: NEFilk 17: Conterpoint 2007; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
        Convention -- NEFilk 17. Conterpoint 2007; CD -- Burnt
      - Conterpoint 2007 publicity flier, NEFilk 17. Conterpoint 2007; 1 copy; Notes: Hot pink flier (on one side only, the other side is white) Origin: Conterpoint 2007, June 22-24, 2007 Convention: NEFilk 17: Conterpoint 2007; genreform: Flier (Box 10)
        Convention -- NEFilk 17. Conterpoint 2007; Flier
      - Conterpoint 2007 Program Book, 1 copy; Notes: Black cover, staple bound Origin: NEFilk 17 Convention: NEFilk 17: Conterpoint 2007; genreform: Program Book (Box 13)
        Convention -- NEFilk 17. Conterpoint 2007; Program Book
      - Programming schedule, 2007; 3 copy; Notes: Black and white grid Origin: NEFilk 17 Convention: NEFilk 17: Conterpoint 2007; genreform: Schedule (Box 13)
        Convention -- NEFilk 17. Conterpoint 2007; Schedule
      - Wild Mercy Eclectic Celtic Electric-Accoustic Quartet: Three Women and a Giraffe Tour, 1 copy; Notes: Green, folded sheet with biographies of the band Convention: NEFIlk 17: Conterpoint 2007; genreform: Program booklet (Box 14)
        Convention -- NEFilk 17. Conterpoint 2007; Program booklet
      - Conterpoint 2007 Program Book, 1 copy; Notes: Black cover with harp spaceship, staple bound Convention: NEFIlk 17: Conterpoint 2007; genreform: Program Book (Box 14)
    - NEFilk 18: Contata 5, 20 Jun 2008 to 22 Jun 2008
      Parsippany, NJ; Convention -- NEFilk 18. Contata 5 (2008); Convention -- NEFilk
      - Contata 2008 Songbook and Program Book, 1 copy; Notes: Blue cover with starship pulling a banner, spiral bound Convention: NEFilk 18: Contata 5: 2008; genreform: Songbook|Program Book (Box 16)
        Convention -- NEFilk 18. Contata 5 (2008); Songbook; Program Book
      - Flier and membership form (torn off), 2007; 1 copy; Notes: Bright orange flier Origin: Contata 5 Convention: NEFilk 18: Contata 5; genreform: Flier (Box 13)
        Convention -- NEFilk 18. Contata 5 (2008); Flier
      - Contata 5 held 2008, June 20-22, 2008, NEFilk 18. Contata 5 (June 20-22, 2008); 1 copy; Notes: Green cover, Spiral bound with I Abra Cinii cover art Origin: Contata 2008, June 20-22, 2008 Convention: NEFilk 18: Contata 5; genreform: Songbook (Box 9)
        Convention -- NEFilk 18. Contata 5 (2008); Songbook
    - NEFilk 19: ConCertino 2009, 19 Jun 2009 to 21 Jun 2009
      Worcester, MA; Convention -- NEFilk 19. ConCertino 2009; Convention -- NEFilk
      - ConCertino 2009 Songbook, 2 copy; Notes: Yellow cover with yowling cat Convention: NEFilk 19: ConCertino 2009; genreform: Songbook|Program Book (Box 16)
        Convention -- NEFilk 19. ConCertino 2009; Songbook; Program Book
      - Eclectic, 2009; Sassafras; Granoff, Matt; Schiller, Lauren; Palmer, Ada; Sound editing by Matt (Granoff), Lauren (Schiller) and Ada (Palmer) and special thanks to Brad Smith from the Second Shift audio drama.; 1 copy; Notes: Live tracks recorded at our Club Passim concert plus new studio recordings Origin: Sound editing by Matt (Granoff), Lauren (Schiller) and Ada (Palmer) and special thanks to Brad Smith from the Second Shift audio drama. Convention: NEFilk 19: ConCertino 2009; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
        Convention -- NEFilk 19. ConCertino 2009; CD -- Commercial
      - CD liner notes and cover for Come Filking with handwritten arrows, 2009; NEFilk 19. Concertino 2009; Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Probably annotated for which way to feed the printer Origin: Floating Filk Studios Convention: NEFilk 19: ConCertino 2009; genreform: Original art (Box 9)
        Convention -- NEFilk 19. ConCertino 2009; Original art
      - Come Filking, 2009; NEFilk 19. Concertino 2009; 2 copy; Origin: Premium CD Convention: NEFilk 19: ConCertino 2009; genreform: Premium CD (Box 1)
        Convention -- NEFilk 19. ConCertino 2009; CD -- Premium
    - NEFilk 20: Conterpoint 2010, 25 Jun 2010 to 27 Jun 2010
      Convention -- NEFilk 20. Conterpoint 2010; Convention -- NEFilk
      - Program Book, June 5-7, 2010; 1 copy; Notes: Spaceship Harp and keyboard on cover, spiral bound Origin: NEFilk 20 Convention: Conterpoint 7; genreform: Songbook|Program Book (Box 13)
        Convention -- NEFilk 20. Conterpoint 2010; Songbook; Program Book
      - Schedule grid, 2010; 3 copy; Notes: Single sided grid Convention: NEFilk 20: Conterpoint 2010; genreform: Schedule (Box 13)
        Convention -- NEFilk 20. Conterpoint 2010; Schedule
      - Conterpoint VII Songbook, 2010; 5 copy; Notes: Beige cover with starship harp and keyboard against the number 20, spiralbound. One copy contains three drawings of rocket ships and a pocket program Convention: NEFilk 20: Conterpoint 2010; genreform: Songbook|Program Book (Box 16)
      - Conterpoint VII Songbook/Program, 1 copy; Notes: White cover, spiral bound with harp spaceship Convention: NEFilk 20: Conterpoint 2010; genreform: Songbook|Program Book (Box 14)
      - Conterpoint 2010 Flier, 1 copy; Notes: Blue filer/registration form Origin: June 25-27, 2010 Convention: NEFilk 20: Conterpoint 2010; genreform: Flier (Box 10)